ACTWU's Murray Finley Records from the President's Office 5619/036
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Indiana New Haven + Penn. Philadelphia Joseph + Cohen + Sons. Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 21)
- Indiana: Portland #TRA, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 22)
- Indiana Rochester Hart Schaffner and Marx Clothes, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 23)
- Iowa Chariton Gross Galesburg Co., 1978 (Box 47, Folder 24)
- Iowa Davenport Robert Tailoring Manufacturing, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 25)
- Iowa Dubuque, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 26)
- Iowa Fairfield + Bonaparte Fairfield Glove co. Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 27)
- Crescendo Gloves, Incorporated Johnston, New York Vermont: St Johnsbury # TRA, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 28)
- Kentucky Mayfield Bryan Manufacturing Co., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 29)
- Kentucky Mayfield Merit Clothing Co., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 30)
- Kentucky Mayfield Bryan MFG Co., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 31)
- Louisiana: New Orleans #849 TRA, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 32)
- Mississippi: Tyertown # TRA, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 33)
- Missouri: Edina # TRA, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 34)
- Missouri: St. Louis #770 TRA, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 35)
- Guy Lewis, Inc Massachusetts: Boston, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 36)
- Leon Clothing MFG., Inc. Massachusetts: Boston # TRA, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 37)
- Mayflower Coat Manufacturing Co. Massachusetts: Brockton # TRA, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 38)
- Massachusetts Cambridge University Clothing corp., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 39)
- Chicopee Coat Company Massachusetts: Chicopee # TRA, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 40)
- Lenwow Manufacturing Company Inc. Massachusetts: Easthampton # TRA, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 41)
- Essex Manufacturing Company, Inc. Massachusetts: Fall River # TRA, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 42)
- Shelburne Shirt Company Massachusetts: Fall River # TRA, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 43)
- San-Roro Manufacturing Company Massachusetts: Fall River # TRA, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 44)
- Stafford Clothing Manufacturing Company Massachusetts: # Fall River, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 45)
- Mass. Fall River Shelbourne Shirt Co., 1977 (Box 47, Folder 46)
- Marlinda Sportswear Massachusetts # Fall River # TRA, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 47)
- Lawrence, Garment Company Massachusetts: Lawrence # TRA, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 48)
- Lanham Clothes, Inc. Massachusetts: Lawrence # TRA, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 49)
- Mass. Lawrence + Stone ham Grieco Brothers Inc., 1977 (Box 47, Folder 50)
- Belont Manufacturing corp. Massachusetts New Bedford # TRA, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 51)
- Mass. New Bedford Bristol Clothing Manufacturing Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 52)
- Dartmouth Clothing Company (Cliftex Corporation,Plant B) Massachusetts: New Bedford # TRA, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 53)
- Deerfield Manufacturing, Inc. Massachusetts: New Bedford, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 54)
- Bristol Clothing Manufacturing, Inc Massachusetts: New Bedford # TRA, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 55)
- Byron Clothing Manufacturing Co. Massachusetts: Somerville # TRA, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 56)
- Modern Shrinking and Refinishing co. Massachusetts: South Boston # TRA, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 57)
- Cliftex Corporation Massachusetts: New Bedford # TRA, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 58)
- Minnesota, Chisholm Gleneagles Division of hart Schaffner + Marx, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 59)
- Maryland Baltimore A. Brashtons Inc., 1975 (Box 47, Folder 60)
- MD - Baltimore - Alberts Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 61)
- Maryland, Baltimore American coat and Pad Company, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 62)
- Maryland Baltimore The hass Tailoring co. Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 63)
- Md. Baltimore Maryland Hampstead co., Hampstead, Maryland + the paramount clothing co., 1975 (Box 47, Folder 64)
- Maryland Baltimore Websters Clothes Inc., 1975 (Box 47, Folder 65)
- Maryland Baltimore superior coat pad co., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 66)
- Maryland Baltimore Western and Cleveland coat front co. Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 67)
- Maryland Baltimore Oakloom clothes Inc., 1975 (Box 47, Folder 68)
- Maryland Baltimore L. Grief + Brothers, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 69)
- Maryland Baltimore Ellison clothes Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 70)
- Maryland Elkton Elkton Fashion co., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 71)
- Md. Frostburg Michael Berkowitz, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 72)
- Md. Westminster Carroll Manufacturing Co. Md Baltimore English American Tailoring co., 1975 (Box 47, Folder 73)
- Cape Cod Sportswear, Inc Massachusetts: New Bedford # TRA, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 74)
- C.F. Hathaway company Inc. Massachusetts: Lowell # TRA, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 75)
- Massachusetts: Lowell # TRA, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 76)
- Star Sportswear Manufacturing co Massachusetts: Lynn # TRA, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 77)
- Joseph H. Cohen & Sons, Inc. New Haven, Ind. And Philadelphia, Penn # TRA, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 78)
- N.J. Bridgetown Major Coat co., 1975 (Box 47, Folder 79)
- N.J. Carteret Carteret Products Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 80)
- N.J Clifton new Jersey Sportswear co., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 81)
- N.J. Elizabeth Chicago sportswear Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 82)
- N.J. Egg Harbor City Jersey Coat co., 1975 (Box 47, Folder 83)
- N.J. Elizabeth Mirando Manufacturing, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 84)
- N.J. Elizabeth Sportswear Inc.., 1980 (Box 47, Folder 85)
- N.J. Elizabeth ACME Leather Sportswear Inc., 1977 (Box 47, Folder 86)
- N.J. Hammonton William B. Kessler Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 87)
- N.J Hammonton Consolidated Pants Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 88)
- N.J Jersey City Americana Coat Co. Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 89)
- N.J Jersey City Hudson Pants co., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 90)
- N.J Newark Century glove Inc., 1977 (Box 47, Folder 91)
- N.J Newark standard glove co. of N.J Inc., 1977 (Box 47, Folder 92)
- N.J Passaic Franksaltz and sons Inc., 1978 (Box 47, Folder 93)
- N.J Passaic M. Ehrenberg sons Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 94)
- N.J Passaic victor Roberts Inc., 1978 (Box 47, Folder 95)
- N.J Perth Amboy Al Peters Shirt co., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 96)
- N.J Roselle Park Gem Sportswear Inc., 1980 (Box 47, Folder 97)
- N.J Perth Amboy AL Peters Shirt co., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 98)
- N.J Red Bank clothing Manufacturing Co. Inc., 1978 (Box 47, Folder 99)
- N.J Trenton Baxters stores Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 100)
- N.J Vineland Model coat co., 1975 (Box 47, Folder 101)
- N.J Vineland Model Coat co., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 102)
- N.J Vineland Crown clothing co., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 103)
- N.J A. Diapoala + co. Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 104)
- N.J Wallington Clifton Clothing, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 105)
- N.J West Orange Style Craft Clothing co., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 106)
- Astors clothes Company, Inc. New York: Brooklyn # TRA, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 107)
- New York: Brooklyn # TRA Gem Arts clothes corporation, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 108)
- New York: Brooklyn # TRA Gem Art Clothes corporation, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 109)
- New York: Brooklyn # TRA Max Kirmayer and Sons, Inc., 1977 (Box 47, Folder 109)
- New York: Brooklyn # TRA Rud-Shaw Clothing, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 110)
- New York, Brooklyn # TRA sportswear Manufacturing Co. Inc., 1977 (Box 47, Folder 111)
- New York Brooklyn # TRA American sportswear, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 112)
- New York, Brooklyn # TRA Albez contractors, Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 113)
- N.Y Brooklyn eagle Pants co., 1977 (Box 47, Folder 114)
- N.Y Brooklyn Fine Craft Cat co. Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 115)
- N.Y Brooklyn. Gulant and Masling Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 116)
- N.Y Brooklyn Howard clothes corp., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 117)
- N.Y Brooklyn Imperial Pants co. Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 118)
- N.Y Brooklyn M'Sieur Slacks Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 119)
- N.Y Brooklyn Robert Hall manufacturing Co., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 120)
- N.Y Brooklyn Howard stores corp., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 121)
- N.Y Corinth The Arrow Com., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 122)
- N.Y Gloversville Joseph Perella Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 123)
- N.Y Gloversville moderne glove co., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 124)
- N.Y Gloversville Ambroson gloves Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 125)
- N.Y Long Island City Sabel +Chaps com., 1978 (Box 47, Folder 126)
- New York, Long Island City # TRA Brookfield Clothes, Inc., 1978 (Box 47, Folder 127)
- N.Y Long Island City Ship Contracting corp., 1978 (Box 47, Folder 128)
- N.Y Long Island City Robert Hall Clothes, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 129)
- N.Y Long Island City herda Contracting co., 1978 (Box 47, Folder 130)
- N.Y New York Arthur Richards, L.T.D, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 131)
- N.Y New York Delton Shirt makers Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 132)
- N.Y New York Charles Dobbs, LTD, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 133)
- N.Y New York Jaeana Sportswear Inc., 1977 (Box 47, Folder 134)
- New York, New York # TRA Grossman, Clothing co. Inc., 1977 (Box 47, Folder 135)
- New York, New York # TRA Slack Fashion, Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 136)
- New York, New York # TRA M. Kopp, Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 137)
- New York, New York # TRA B. Galnzrock, Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 138)
- New York, New York # TRA Rarra Hall Clothes, Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 139)
- N.Y New York delton LTD, + George Heller Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 140)
- N.Y New York + N.Y. Oceanside Dino Clothing co., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 141)
- N.Y New York City Benjamin Flax Inc., 1975 (Box 47, Folder 142)
- N.Y New York Tischler and Benkel com, Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 143)
- N.Y New York Sidmar clothing co. Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 144)
- N.Y. New York Sanrie Sportswear Inc., 1977 (Box 47, Folder 145)
- N.Y New York spilton brothers Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 146)
- N.Y New York Crescent Destasio Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 147)
- N.Y New York Cohns Clothing co. Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 148)
- N.Y New York Moda Contracting corporation Division of Petrocelli clothes Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 149)
- N.Y New York Enzel-Arthur Richards Manufacturing corp., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 150)
- N. Y. New York vicale- Catiania clothing, LTD, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 151)
- N.Y New York Andrew Pallack + Co, Inc. Bruce Ramse Division of Andrew Pallack, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 152)
- N.Y New York brookwale Manufacturing co., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 153)
- N.Y. New York Arthur Richards LTD, Enzel-Arthur Richards E.A.R Pants MFG corp., 1977 (Box 47, Folder 154)
- N.Y New York Hy-Grade Sportswear co. Inc + Hy-Grade coat co. Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 155)
- N.Y New York City Grossman clothing co. Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 156)
- New York, New York # TRA Catania Clothing Corporation, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 157)
- New York, New York # TRA Eduardi Bonelli and co. Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 158)
- New York, New York # TRA Arrow Clothes, Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 159)
- New York, New York # TRA Ambassador Clothes, Inc and Fashion Tailors, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 160)
- N.Y. New York Grossman Clothing co. Inc., 1977 (Box 47, Folder 161)
- N.Y New York Mada Contracting corp., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 162)
- N.Y New York boulet Sportswear LTD, Inc., 1977 (Box 47, Folder 163)
- N.Y New York Andrew Pallack + co. Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 164)
- N.Y New York Sussex Clothes, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 165)
- N.Y New York Saint Lanrie LTD., 1978 (Box 47, Folder 166)
- N.Y New York Quality coat com. Inc, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 167)
- N.Y New York Primo Coat corp., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 168)
- N.Y New York Primer Clothing co., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 169)
- N.Y New York Mr. Ned Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 170)
- N.Y New York A.S. Mines Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 171)
- N.Y New York Mandlebaim Coat co., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 172)
- N.Y New York the Everette Levinsohn corp., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 173)
- N.Y New York Lefeton Custom Tailors, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 174)
- N.Y Troy Marshall Ray corp., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 175)
- N.Y Richmond Hill Dirzis Products Company Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 176)
- N.C Greensboro Cone Mills corp., 1977 (Box 47, Folder 177)
- Ohio Cincinnati Shaefer tailoring Company Inc., 1977 (Box 47, Folder 178)
- Ohio Cincinnati Maxwell + Rothchild Inc., 1978 (Box 47, Folder 179)
- H.A Seinsheimer Company Ohio: Cincinnati # TRA, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 180)
- Ohio Cincinnati Shaeffer Tailoring Co. Inc., 1977 (Box 47, Folder 181)
- Ohio Cincinnati H.A, Seinsheimer, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 182)
- Ohio Cincinnati Mack Shirt co., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 183)
- Ohio Cincinnati Hutch Sporting Goods co., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 184)
- Ohio Cincinnati Hochscheid Tailoring co., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 185)
- Ohio Columbus Hercules Transfer co. Inc., 1977 (Box 47, Folder 186)
- Penn. Easton Strongwear Slacks co. Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 187)
- Penn. Easton Northampton Pants co., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 188)
- Penn Easton Lake Manufacturing co. Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 189)
- Penn. Easton Strongwear Pants co. Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 190)
- Penn. Philadelphia Caliper Clothes Inc., 1975 (Box 47, Folder 191)
- Penn. Philadelphia Sun Clothes Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 192)
- Penn. Philadelphia Imperial clothes co., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 193)
- Penn. Philadelphia Jacob Seigel co, Inc., 1975 (Box 47, Folder 194)
- Penn. Philadelphia Teplick Clothes, Incorporated, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 195)
- Penn. Philadelphia Stanley,Inc. Coordinated Transfers Inc. Patgat Clothes Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 196)
- Penn. Philadelphia Scotese Brothers, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 197)
- Penn. Philadelphia Penn State Clothing corp., 1975 (Box 47, Folder 198)
- Penn. Philadelphia Nick Ippoliti Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 199)
- Penn Philadelphia Modern Coat co., 1975 (Box 47, Folder 200)
- Penn. Philadelphia The Middishade co. Inc., 1975 (Box 47, Folder 201)
- Penn. Philadelphia Michael Incorporated, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 202)
- Penn. Philadelphia J Maimon + Sons Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 203)
- Penn. Philadelphia Charles H. Liebman + Brothers Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 204)
- Penn. Philadelphia Fashionbuilt Clothes Division of Chips n Twigs Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 205)
- Penn Philadelphia max Golden + Sons Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 206)
- PA. Philadelphia Lawrence Clothes Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 207)
- Penn. Philadelphia Keystone Uniform Manufacturing Company, Inc., 1975 (Box 47, Folder 208)
- Penn. Philadelphia K+D Clothing Manufacturing co., 1978 (Box 47, Folder 209)
- Penn Philadelphia Cross Country Clothes, Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 210)
- Penn. Philadelphia Fulton Clothes co. Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 211)
- Penn. Philadelphia Gentry Clothing co., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 212)
- Penn. Philadelphia A. Giaracino + Sons, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 213)
- Penn. Philadelphia Fashionbilt clothes Davison of chips n Twigs Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 214)
- Penn. Philadelphia Modern Cloth Sponging co., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 215)
- Penn. Philadelphia Victory Clothes co. Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 216)
- Penn. Philadelphia Fulto Clothes Co. Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 217)
- Penn. Philadelphia Magerman Trousers, Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 218)
- Penn. Philadelphia Star supporter Manufacturing co. Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 219)
- Penn. Philadelphia MLM Sportswear, Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 220)
- Penn Philadelphia Royal Clothing co. Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 221)
- Penn. Philadelphia Baker clothes Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 222)
- Penn Philadelphia Progressive Uniform Manufacturing corp., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 223)
- Penn Huntington The Arrow Company, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 224)
- Penn Northampton Modern Slack Creations, Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 225)
- Penn. Frackville Charles Robin + co. Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 226)
- Penn Lansdale The Puritan co. Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 227)
- Penn. Northampton Cross Country Clothes Inc., 1975 (Box 47, Folder 228)
- Penn. Pen Argyt R+R toy Manufacturing co. Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 229)
- Penn. Uniontown (Route. 51) Michael Berkowitz co. Inc., 1978 (Box 47, Folder 230)
- Pennsylvania Waynesburg Michael Berkowitz co. Inc., 1977 (Box 47, Folder 231)
- S.C Greenville Burlington Industries, Inc., 1977 (Box 47, Folder 232)
- Manhattan Shirt Company, Inc. South Carolina: Winnsboro # TRA, 19776 (Box 47, Folder 233)
- Tennessee: Clarksville # TRA, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 234)
- Tennessee: Dickson # TRA, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 235)
- Tennessee: Lawrenceburg # TRA, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 236)
- Tennessee Martin # TRA, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 237)
- Tenn. Nashville Phoenix clothes, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 238)
- Tennessee Oneida Boss Manufacturing co., 1977 (Box 47, Folder 239)
- Oneida: Tennessee # TRA, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 240)
- Tennessee: Tiptonville # TRA, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 241)
- Texas New Braunfels Aldon Inc., 1977 (Box 47, Folder 242)
- Texas San Antonio + New Braunfels Aldon Inc., 1977 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- VA Fredericksburg Rappahannock Sportswear Co. Inc., 1977 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- W. VA. Elkins Reidbord Brothers co. Inc., 1977 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- W. VA Morganstown Morgan Shirt Co., 1977 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Wisconsin Marinette Milwaukee glove co., 1976 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Wisconsin Milwaukee Apex glove co. Inc., 1976 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Wisconsin Rio + Oconto Racine glove co., 1976 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- TRA, 1979-1980 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- TRA/Individuals, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- TRA/Articles, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- TRA/Appeals, 1975-1977 (Box 48, Folder 11)
- TRA/Problems, 1975-1977 (Box 48, Folder 12)
- TRA/Reports, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 13)
- TRA/Background forms, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 14)
- TRA, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 15)
- TRA New York State, 1976-1977 (Box 48, Folder 16)
- Trade Adjustment Assistance Philadelphia # 1, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 17)
- Theresa Affronti H. Sigelbaum, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Doris Feliciano for Florencio Alequin M. Moreno, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Luigi Alparone Ins. Co., 1982 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Anderson Little co. fall River, Mass. E. Clark, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Dorothy Ansell Ins. Co., 1983 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Barbara J. Antonio Swoboda, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Deana Babrawski Loevy and Dropkin, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Deana (Kelly) Barbrawski Loevy and Dropkin (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Artime, Josephine, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Florencio Balleste, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Genevieve Baradics Ins. Co., 1981 (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Bemmy Barbarossa L. Calder, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Grace Barry, Local 347 H. Dropkin, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Evelyn Bash Ins. Co., 1982 (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Francis A. Berry Willis Opperman, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 14)
- Jeanette Billingsley G. Ferraris, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 15)
- Raffaele Blango A. Georgian, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 16)
- Josephine Boncone, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 17)
- Ruth S. Bordwine, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 18)
- Little Boys (dec) (H. Sigelbaum), 1982 (Box 49, Folder 19)
- Winifred Bradberry Ins Co., 1982 (Box 49, Folder 20)
- Sarsa Bradmon Sigelbaum, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 21)
- Debra Breininger Carita, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 22)
- Mary R. Britt Sigelbaum, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 23)
- Dolores Brown Claude Cox, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 24)
- Bernice bulgatz, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 25)
- Dolores Buanno Harvey Sigelbaum, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 26)
- Valerie Burgess Garry Ferraris, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 27)
- Maxine I Buzzanca H. Dropkin, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 28)
- Alice L. Price Art Loevy, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 29)
- Local 1445 - Carl Hill-S-T Bruce Dunton, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 30)
- Charity A. Gsell (Ferraris/ Stevens), 1984 (Box 49, Folder 31)
- Local 383 Salisbury, MD(Ferraris/Sigelbaum), 1984 (Box 49, Folder 32)
- Hope M. Cahoon Scott Hoyman, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 33)
- Eudino Camara, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 34)
- Robert Carter Scott Hoyman, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 35)
- Charles Caruso Ins. Co., 1981 (Box 49, Folder 36)
- Sarah Ceccarelli Local 125 N. Aiello, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 37)
- Mary Jane Chaney (Martil Clothing Co.) J. Fox, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 38)
- Ramona Chase, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 39)
- Alice Christopher Dunton, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 40)
- Jean Clapp (Merit Clothing Co.) L. Spitzer, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 41)
- Coleman Clothes Hialeah, Fla. C. English, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 42)
- Joseph Consalvi Ins. Co., 1981 (Box 49, Folder 43)
- Marilyn Rustom, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 44)
- E. Consenzer H. Sigelbaum, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 45)
- Frances Hershey D. Myers, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 46)
- Margaret Wanamaker J. Fox, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 47)
- Louise Clippinger H. sigelbaum, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 48)
- Emma Johnson john Fox, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 49)
- Jeannette R. Rogers J. Jackson, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 50)
- Lillian Bieniak Mary Kunath, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 51)
- Ruth Wanger, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 52)
- Lawrence A. Puca Pompilio Pasquini, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 53)
- Anthony D'Amico, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 54)
- Juan Jose Acevedo, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 55)
- Mary Meeks, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 56)
- Angelina Dileo, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 57)
- Gladys Miller, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 58)
- Ralph Contento, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 59)
- Richard A. Kessler, 1986-1987 (Box 49, Folder 60)
- Catherine MacInnis C. Clark, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 61)
- Monica Cradduck J. Craven, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 62)
- John R. Smith W. Hall, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 63)
- Local 181 E. Clark, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 64)
- Mary Ann Ferreira M. Defazio, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 65)
- Yvonne Weishar vs, Jerome danin, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 66)
- Louis Roth Members, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 67)
- Grace Waller, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 68)
- Margaret Ann Houston, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 69)
- Angela Howard W. Hall, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 70)
- L. Welsh for Beatrice Solowinski (Charles), 1986 (Box 49, Folder 71)
- Alice G. Savary, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 72)
- Mae Julia Booker, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 73)
- Alatex, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 74)
- Nancy Vickers, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 75)
- William Cheers, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 76)
- Paolo Alleca, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 77)
- Martha Rath, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 78)
- Billie Morgan (Jamie Jackson), 1985 (Box 49, Folder 79)
- Rose K. Mclain A. Loevy, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 80)
- Roberta Brock Jackson/Ferraria, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 81)
- Patrick Radika Frank Nicholas Richard Rothstien, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 82)
- Evelyn Gentile, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 83)
- Mildred Meyer H. Sigelbaum, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 84)
- Elsie Smith, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 85)
- Draleen Shuler Art Jones, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 86)
- Maureen Jaffrey L. Calder, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 87)
- Mary Singer, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 88)
- Brenda Howard, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 89)
- Mrs. James graham, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 90)
- Darrell Lee, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 91)
- Marcia Ricci T. Thompson, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 92)
- Deloris Cox G. Ferraris, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 93)
- Gail Paulos G. Ferraris, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 94)
- William J. Tunney, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 95)
- Poco Tech Ind., 1986 (Box 49, Folder 96)
- Herman Rosanetz, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 97)
- Patricia Poskey, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 98)
- Eleanor Kuterbach D. Myers, 1984-1985 (Box 49, Folder 99)
- Virginia L. Humphreys, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 100)
- Local 963, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 101)
- Meredith Jeffries, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 102)
- Lillian Sanchez, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 103)
- Gabriel Robles, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 104)
- Local 281- Sheila Childress, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 105)
- Carole Ulysses, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 106)
- Bentley Cawley R. Radio, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 107)
- Mary L. Smith H. Sigelbaum, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 108)
- Dee Delp B. Dunton, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 109)
- Angie Horn (Garry Ferraris), 1985 (Box 49, Folder 110)
- Richard Lewis, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 111)
- Grace Tagliabue H. Sigelbaum, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 112)
- Local 710T C. Sallee, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 113)
- Elizabeth Foldi H. Sigelbaum, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 114)
- Caroline Harris G. Ferraris, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 115)
- Evelyn Larson H. Sigelbaum, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 116)
- Joan Marburger, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 117)
- Jane Chavvis, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 118)
- Catherine Rosseau R. Rothstein, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 119)
- Lenore Frances Lewis, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 120)
- A General, 1984-1985 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Bank of New York, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- American Federation of State County & Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1984 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Articles, 1985-1987 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- "C" General, 1984-1987 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Cotton Garment Fund, 1983-1986 (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Cotton Garment Negotiations 1985 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Crafted with Pride, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 8)